{
    "id": "ee67042a720d49bf9ea03eaa6e3ae539",
    "title": "Subject And Object Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It took …………….. twenty minutes to get dressed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She told ……………. an interesting story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think we should wait for ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You pay for your drinks and I will pay for …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mine",
                "my"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am angry with both of ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you like ……………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Are ………………. coming with us?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was very kind of ……………. to help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Did ………………. recognize ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her, him",
                "she, him",
                "she, he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you speak to ………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}